I agree and authorize: i. That the Company will be on risk in pursuance of this proposal for insurance only after the risk under the Proposal Form is accepted by the Company and such acceptance is communicated to me in writing by the Company. ii. That the Company shall be entitled to retain the premium paid along with the Proposal Form as an interest free initial deposit to be adjusted against premium payable upon issuance of the Policy. In the event the proposal for insurance is not accepted by the Company the aforesaid deposit shall be refunded without any interest subject to deductions for medical costs and processing charges, if any. iii. My past and present employers / business associates, any doctor/medical examiner / hospital / laboratory / clinic / insurance company (notwithstanding any usage or custom or rules/ regulations of such hospital or laboratory or clinic) to disclose and furnish such documents regarding my employment/business, my health and habits or health and habits of the Life to be Assured (without taking the prior consent of my family or of any member thereof) to the Company as it may require either for the purpose of processing my proposal for insurance or at any time thereafter for any other purpose in relation to the Policy that may be issued in pursuance of this proposal for insurance. iv. That the Company may, without any reference to me or my family or any member thereof, furnish any details/ information furnished in this Proposal Form to any judicial or statutory or other authority or to any insurer or reinsurer in connection with the processing of this proposal for insurance or for any other purpose (for e.g. settlement of a claim). v. That in addition to postal or courier service, the Company may, at its discretion use any electronic media / registered email id, for communicating with me. vi. That I have voluntarily given my consent to collect, process, receive, possess, store, deal or handle my/our sensitive personal data or information [as defined in the Information Technology (Reasonable security practices and procedures and sensitive personal data or information) Rules 2011 as amended from time to time],Data with third parties/ vendors associated with the Company for various purposes and outsourced activities exclusively related to issuance/servicing/settlement of claim as required under the Policy.
